<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions">
Terms and Conditions

1. Acceptance of Terms
By accessing or using the BeautyCam application ("the App"), you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not use the App.

2. User Responsibility and Content Liability
2.1. You are solely responsible for all activities conducted through your account and any content you create, upload, share, or transmit using the App.
2.2. The App and its owners explicitly disclaim any responsibility or liability for user-generated content or user actions.
2.3. You agree to indemnify and hold harmless the App, its owners, employees, and affiliates from any claims arising from your use of the App.

3. Compliance with Laws
3.1. Indian Information Technology Act, 2000
- You must comply with all provisions of the IT Act, 2000 and its amendments.
- Any unauthorized access to computer systems is prohibited under Section 43 and 66.
- Sharing of obscene or offensive content is prohibited under Section 67.

3.2. International Laws
- Users must comply with their local laws and regulations regarding content sharing and digital communications.
- The App complies with GDPR for European users and CCPA for California residents.

4. Prohibited Activities
You agree not to:
- Post illegal, harmful, or offensive content
- Impersonate others or misrepresent your identity
- Harass, bully, or harm other users
- Distribute malware or engage in hacking activities
- Infringe on intellectual property rights
- Use the App for any illegal purposes

5. Content Moderation and Removal
5.1. The App reserves the right to:
- Remove any content that violates these terms
- Suspend or terminate accounts for violations
- Report illegal activities to law enforcement
5.2. Users can report violations through the App\'s reporting system

6. Privacy and Data Protection
6.1. Data collection and usage are governed by our Privacy Policy
6.2. Users retain ownership of their content but grant the App license to use it
6.3. The App implements reasonable security measures but cannot guarantee absolute security

7. Limitation of Liability
7.1. The App is provided "as is" without warranties of any kind
7.2. We are not liable for:
- User-generated content
- Loss of data or profits
- Service interruptions
- Any indirect, consequential, or incidental damages

8. Intellectual Property
8.1. The App and its original content are protected by copyright and other IP laws
8.2. Users retain rights to their content but grant the App a worldwide license to use it

9. Governing Law and Jurisdiction
9.1. These terms are governed by Indian law
9.2. Any disputes shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of courts in India
9.3. For international users, mandatory local laws may also apply

10. Changes to Terms
10.1. We reserve the right to modify these terms at any time
10.2. Continued use after changes constitutes acceptance
10.3. Users will be notified of significant changes

11. Termination
11.1. We may terminate or suspend access to the App immediately without prior notice
11.2. All provisions of the Terms which should survive termination shall survive

12. Contact Information
For any questions about these Terms, please contact us at support@beautycam.com

By using this App, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions.
    </string>
</resources>
